<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 09:28:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Kafka - When to commit?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-commit-strategies/
            </link>
            <description>
                In a previous blog post, we have looked at failure strategies provided by the Reactive Messaging Kafka connector. But, imagine it&#8217;s our lucky day, and for once it worked. We should inform Kafka that the processing succeeded. In Kafka terminology, we call this: offset commit. This post covers the different...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-commit-strategies/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus native running on a Raspberry Pi</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-native-on-a-raspberry-pi/
            </link>
            <description>
                Intro When I&#8217;ve been introduced to Quarkus, back in December 2018, I suddenly had the feeling the Quarkus runtime has the potential of covering ~95% of the software use-cases. My friend Sanne demoed Quarkus on his laptop when the runtime was still in an alpha state, far from being the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-native-on-a-raspberry-pi/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.9.1.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-9-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Thanks to all your feedback, here comes 1.9.1.Final with bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using Quarkus 1.9. If you are not using 1.9 already, please refer to the 1.9 migration guide. What&#8217;s new? This release is a maintenance release that fixes various bugs found...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-9-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Mutiny - Flow control and Back-pressure</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-back-pressure/
            </link>
            <description>
                Reactive Programming offers an elegant, flexible, and powerful way to write asynchronous code. It supports failure handling, both sequential and parallel operation composition, and plenty of operators. Reactive programming promotes data streams as a primary construct, and your code is observing streams and reacting to signals. Figure 1. Origins of...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-back-pressure/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Experimental GraphQL</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/experimental_graphql/
            </link>
            <description>
                This blog post is a follow up on the initial introductory post, Supersonic Subatomic GraphQL, and here we will explore more features, some that is experimental, that we hope to eventually move to the MicroProfile GraphQL Specification (based on your feedback !) We will look at the following: Operational Context...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/experimental_graphql/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.9 released - Micrometer extension maturing, multiple Redis clients, Quarkiverse</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-9-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus 1.9 comes with a lot of improvements on top of our existing feature set: The Micrometer extension is maturing Kafka now has metrics Multiple Redis clients are supported (as well as Sentinel connections) Bean Validation is supported by Reactive Routes SmallRye Reactive Messaging upgraded to 2.4.0 and Mutiny to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-9-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Kafka - How to fail gracefully</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-failure-strategy/
            </link>
            <description>
                Failures are inevitable. There is nothing we can do about that, and that also applies to Kafka applications. Your application may contain a faulty component misbehaving once in a while, or unable to process a specific Kafka record. In this post, we are going to see how we can manage...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-failure-strategy/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Micrometer is recommended for metrics with Quarkus 1.9</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/micrometer-metrics/
            </link>
            <description>
                Though Quarkus offers extensions for MicroProfile, including metrics, we&#8217;re now recommending the use of the Micrometer extension for metrics in Quarkus with the release of 1.9. Brief MicroProfile Metrics History During the creation of the MicroProfile Metrics specification in 2017, Dropwizard Metrics was the most popular metrics library at that...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/micrometer-metrics/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Mutiny - How does retry... retries?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/uni-retry/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, David, a Quarkus user, asked me about retrying an asynchronous operation. David has a picky remote HTTP service, which sometimes misbehaves. Easy answer! Just do: uni.onFailure().retry().atMost(x). But, David is curious, and asked me a second question: how does retry work? Well, that’s simple; it just retries&#8230;&#8203; As you...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/uni-retry/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.2.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.2.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.2.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release brings enhanced support for Eclipse Microprofile. Eclipse Microprofile Reactive Messaging If your application is based on Eclipse Microprofile Reactive Messaging, properties are enabled for: @Connector annotation @Outgoing annotation @Incoming annotation Here is an example...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.2.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
